我认为可以把Intent看作信封，
I like to think of intents as envelopes
里边包含了一个目标，比如在这里表示你想把消息发送给哪个组件
each one includes who, or in this case, which component you want it
而且Intent里面还有空间可以
delivered to. And there's room for a small amount of data to be delivered,
以Extra的方式存储一些少量的数据
packaged as extras.
应用程序中有效的原始数据结构
Primitive tuples that will be available to the application
才能最终得到并打开这个Intent对象。
component that ultimately receives and opens this intent. So an
所以一个显式声明的Intent需要显示声明接收者的名称，
explicit intent, explicitly specifies the name of the recipient, as
就像你在这个信封上看到的一样。隐式Intent就更有意思了。
you can see on this envelope. Implicit intents are a
这里，我们并不指定这个类的名称。
lot more interesting. Here, we don't specify the name of
我们甚至不知道他是什么。所以，
the class. We don't even know what it is. So,
那我们如何知道需要打开哪个activity呢？
how do we indicate which activity to launch? Well, you
你也许知道这样的故事，你是否有时候听说过有的信用的是
know those stories you sometimes hear about letters with fake
假地址，但是依旧可以找到去往收件人地址的路线？
addresses like these that somehow still find their way to the intended
安卓系统的Intent解析也是一样的工作原理。
recipient? Well the intent resolution system on Android, works the same way.
找到一个activity，它能够执行一个你
Finding an activity, capable of performing an action
对相关数据的操作。所以，与其指定
you specify on the associated data. So, rather than
一个类名称，你要指定
specifying the name of a class, you indicate
一个activity要执行的操作
an action you'd like an activity to perform, and
和它对数据要进行的操作。
on what data that action should be performed.
就像这样，我们想要打开一个activity，
Like this, where we want to address an activity
它能用来浏览网页。因为Intent可以
that's capable of viewing a website. And because intents
可以跨越程序进行传递，而所打开的activity
can cross through application boundaries, the activity that started,
很可能都不是你的应用程序的activity。所以，
may not be part of your app. So,
你可以像这样添加功能，比如浏览网页、
you can include functionality like this, browsing websites or
打电话或是从电话本里选择联系人。
making phone calls or choosing a contact from your address book. All
这些功能都可以从你的应用里打开，而你不用去实现这些功能。
from within your app, without you having to implement any of it yourself.
你甚至不需要知道哪个应用
You don't even need to know about the app
最终完成了你的请求。你可以在
that will ultimately service your request. You can find
安卓开发者的网站的 Common Intents 页面里了解到
details of some of the intents supported by native
原生程序所支持的intent。
apps in Common Intents page of the Android developer site.